imc-companies.com 2019-07-31

# 

Privacy Statement
Your privacy as well as the protection of all of your personal information is vitally important to
us. We undertake to safeguard them by exercising reasonable care and using reasonably
available means.
Personal Data
IMC International Metalworking Companies BV, its subsidiaries and affiliates ("IMC") may
collect certain personal data, such as name, email address, country of residence and any other
information that you choose to share in the course of using this site.
YOU ARE NOT OBLIGED TO PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, although it may
be required in connection with the services and/or to use features of this site, such as making
purchases and receive updated information regarding our products.
Controller
IMC will be acting as the controller of the personal information you submit while using this site.
Legal bases and purposes for the processing of personal data
IMC may process your personal data based on, among others, (i) the performance of a contract;
(ii) a legitimate interest; (iii) compliance with a legal obligation or (iv) your consent. If your
personal data is processed solely based on consent, you will at all times have the right to
withdraw your consent.
We may process your personal data for the following purposes:
      •   We may use the information for statistical and marketing purposes, in order to analyze
          and process your preferences and varying needs and to contact you for the purpose of
          providing you with details and features related to our products, our services and/or to
          the contents of our site.
      •   We may further use the information when it is required under applicable law or in course
          of any legal proceedings.
      •   Our site may gather certain usage information, such as numbers and frequency of
          visitors to our site. This information may be used by us solely in the aggregate to enable
          us to improve the access, the availability, the various features and contents of our site,
          and in order to assure that it may appeal to, and be used by as many users as possible.
We may make use of certain technologies, such as cookies, which process statistical data and
provide details regarding the number of visitors to our site, the means by which access is made
to the site, and the times of visiting our site. We do not use such technologies to collect
personally identifiable information, nor do we use any data received through same with other
personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
We may further use functions from the web analysis service 'Google Analytics'. For more details
pertaining         'Google        Analytics'     and      your      rights       thereunder      see
www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.
Retention Period
We retain the personal information you provide while your account is active, or as needed to
provide you services with respect to purchases made through this site, unless we are required
by law to store your personal data longer.

YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THIS SITE, OR OF ANY PART THEREOF, CONSTITUTES
YOUR ACKNOWLEDGMENT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND OUR PRIVACY
STATEMENT.
Your Rights
In connection with your personal data that we may process, you, as a data subject, have the
following rights:
               (i)    Right to request to obtain access to the personal data concerning you;
               (ii)   Right to request rectification or correction of your personal data;
               (iii) Right to request erasure of the personal data concerning you;
               (iv) Right to request restricting the processing;
               (v)    Right to request data portability;
               (vi) Right to object to profiling;
               (vii) The right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority;
               (viii) The right to withdraw your consent.
The above stated rights can be exercised by submitting a request to: imccompliance@imc.co.il.
We shall assess whether we can honor your request. We shall timely provide you with an
appropriate response to your request.
Any information received by us in connection with a transaction or agreement with you, that we
received from you over the Internet is generally regarded as confidential information, unless
the information is already publicly available or not of a confidential nature.
Sharing of personal data
We may share personal information processed as a result from your use of this site with other
members of the IMC Group, to be used for the same purposes for which such personal
information was originally collected. We may also share information with our authorized
distributors and/or dealers for the purpose of facilitating transactions you may wish to conduct
with us, with the aim to better meet your needs. Other than the above, we do not disclose any
information that we receive from you to any other third party without your prior consent, nor do
we sell or rent any information received from you.
Such sharing of the personal information shall be made with third parties who are either located
in Israel, country ensuring an "adequate level of protection" under the GDPR, or to third parties
whose engagement with us includes Standard Contractual Clauses, as required under the
GDPR to ensure adequate level of protection of personal data.
Contact
If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement and/or the processing of
personal data please contact us via: imccompliance@imc.co.il.
© IMC International Metalworking Companies B.V. All Rights Reserved [May 2018]
